<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Bailey Lockheart: Updates</title>
<link>https://baileylockheart.neocities.org/updates</link>
<item>
<title>♡ RSS Feed ♡</title>
<link>https://baileylockheart.neocities.org/updates</link>
<guid>https://baileylockheart.neocities.org/updates</guid>
<pubDate>Mar. 23, 2024</pubDate>
<description>I MADE AN RSS FEED 🤩🤩🤩 I felt like I didn't really update this thing enough, and I could just FEEL that it was bc I didn't want to go on my computer to update the html file. Bc of that, I made a little rss feed and stuck it on github so I can use it from my phone!</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Country music????</title>
<link>https://www.threads.net/@bailey_lockheart/post/C4pLY5gOoSO</link>
<guid>https://www.threads.net/@bailey_lockheart/post/C4pLY5gOoSO</guid>
<pubDate>Mar. 17, 2024</pubDate>
<description>I FORGOT TO MENTION THIS, but I posted a song that I co-wrote and performed on yt a while back, and today my dad said it popped up on his reccomended as a part of a playlist of country music??? like, I have nothing against country music, but I had no idea that I'd written any 😭😭💀</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>♡ Small Update ♡</title>
<link>https://baileylockheart.neocities.org/updates</link>
<guid>https://baileylockheart.neocities.org/updates</guid>
<pubDate>Mar. 11, 2024</pubDate>
<description>RECORDING IN PROGRESS 🤩🤩 aaaand also I'm considering adding onto this website 👀 it's a fun little site but I want to make it MORE fun, yknow? idk how I'm gonna do it, but I'll certainly give it a try!</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>♡ RSS Feed ♡</title>
<link>https://www.threads.net/@bailey_lockheart/post/C23qeVyLR6I</link>
<guid>https://www.threads.net/@bailey_lockheart/post/C23qeVyLR6I</guid>
<pubDate>Feb. 2, 2024 19:07:00 PST</pubDate>
<description>I wanna learn to do more electronic-y music production 😭😭 it seems so fun + the timing might be easier since you can quantize stuff (or whatever it is) as opposed to trying to line it all up with my 53rd messy take of guitar</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>♡ Procrastination ♡</title>
<link>https://baileylockheart.tumblr.com/post/739647921344184321/i-have-a-song-i-should-be-working-on-and-i-have</link>
<guid>https://baileylockheart.tumblr.com/post/739647921344184321/i-have-a-song-i-should-be-working-on-and-i-have</guid>
<pubDate>Jan. 15, 2024</pubDate>
<description>I have a song I SHOULD be working on and I have some songs I WANT to be working on but I will be working on NONE OF THEM</description>
</item>
<item>
<item>
<title>♡ Songwriting Update ♡</title>
<link>https://baileylockheart.neocities.org/updates</link>
<guid>https://baileylockheart.neocities.org/updates</guid>
<pubDate>Oct. 18, 2023</pubDate>
<description>songwriting inspo feels really weird sometimes 🥲 planning out a three song EP, writing a few songs over a week, and now having to sort out a NINE SONG ALBUM??? wild. I miiiight have to cut a song for time, hopefully not, but I wanna get things going!</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>♡ Microblog ♡</title>
<link>https://baileylockheart.neocities.org/updates</link>
<guid>https://baileylockheart.neocities.org/updates</guid>
<pubDate>Sept. 22, 2023</pubDate>
<description>HEYYYYYYY DIY MICROBLOG??? This whole thing is HEAVILY based on Threads, but I wanted to make something to see if I could! turns out, it's not as hard as I thought it'd be 👀 this doesn't even REALLY have to be a microblog, since there's no character limit! I think this is will be a fun little place for updates and announcements!</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>♡ New Layout: The Sequel ♡</title>
<link>https://baileylockheart.neocities.org/updates</link>
<guid>https://baileylockheart.neocities.org/updates</guid>
<pubDate>Sept. 17, 2023</pubDate>
<description>uhhhh oops, I redid the whole site bc it was so bad on mobile that it hurt my brain 🥲 aaaanyway, I think this layout's much better than the previous one, so we'll see how it goes!</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>♡ New Layout ♡</title>
<link>https://baileylockheart.neocities.org/updates</link>
<guid>https://baileylockheart.neocities.org/updates</guid>
<pubDate>Aug. 26, 2023</pubDate>
<description>NEW LAYOUTTTTTT 🤩🤩 I coded all of it myself and I'm very proud of it 🥹💖 it might be a little messy right now, but I'm working on it!</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>♡ A Different Place Release! ♡</title>
<link>https://baileylockheart.neocities.org/updates</link>
<guid>https://baileylockheart.neocities.org/updates</guid>
<pubDate>Aug. 20, 2023</pubDate>
<description>I APPARENTLY MADE A MISTAKE, I THOUGHT IT WAS GONNA BE IN MY LOCAL TIMEZONE BUT I THINK IT WAS IN EST, AAAAAA-</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
