<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Bailey Lockheart // Updates</title>
        <description>Site Updates!</description>
        <link>https://bailey.lockheart.love/</link>
        <item>
            <title>★ Beepbox! ★</title>
            <description>The overhaul is complete, and I'm onto making new things! I'm making a few short videos to post later, and I've also been playing around in beepbox recently, which I'm having a lot of fun with! Hopefully more fun things are to come ^^</description>
            <link>https://bailey.lockheart.love/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-21</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 15:04:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>★ New Feed! ★</title>
            <description>I'm still working on that overhaul, and it'll likely take me at least another day or two, but I redid the structure of this RSS feed to make it a valid feed!!</description>
            <link>https://bailey.lockheart.love/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-20</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 22:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>♡ Overhaul Time ♡</title>
            <link>https://bailey.lockheart.love/</link>
            <description>This website has existed in some form or another for over two years now, and it hasn't changed much (visually) in that time, even though I feel like I've changed a lot as a person. Because of that, I'm going to be attempting a complete and total overhaul for this website, as well as my general "brand" if you could call it that? I'll be archiving the current layout, so it won't disappear, but hopefully the newer one will be more fitting :D</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-19</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 21:19:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>♡ Friendly Web! ♡</title>
            <link>https://bailey.lockheart.love/</link>
            <description>Even though this is my more-professional website, I really wanted to connect it to the personal web as I like it. I mean, it's hand-coded by me, so why not? So, I moved my link button and webrings to the front page! I'm trying to figure out the extent to which I'll link to other sites, and I'm sure that if I ever go 10000% professional, this stuff would have to go to a dedicated page instead, but for now, I'm really happy with it :3</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-18</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:14:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>♡ Domain Time! ♡</title>
            <link>https://bailey.lockheart.love/</link>
            <description>I've officially moved this site over to my own domain (bailey.lockheart.love)! The previous link (baileylockheart.netlify.app) will continue to work, but this is the new, improved, and preferred one!</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-17</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 14:56:00 -0800</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>♡ Small Update! ♡</title>
            <link>https://bailey.lockheart.love/</link>
            <description>I've been working on recording my next big project for quite a while now, and it's taking WAYYYY longer than expected ㅠㅠ however! in the meantime, I'm working on putting up more videos on youtube, both originals and a few covers ^^ I don't have an uploading schedule or anything, but generally, I'm gonna try to make videos more often, while still recording as well!!</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-16</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 22:20:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>♡ One Year ♡</title>
            <link>https://www.threads.net/@bailey_lockheart/post/C-OEdHfyGRN</link>
            <description>WAIT IT'S BEEN A YEAR SINCE I WROTE BIG HUG ALREADY OMG</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-15</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 12:40:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>♡ Motivation ♡</title>
            <link>https://www.threads.net/@bailey_lockheart/post/C8vg5ueJjWU</link>
            <description>why is my motivation like this 😭😭😭 I have covid rn but NOW, ALL OF A SUDDEN, I want to record music and make content and get back into doing volleyball drills and walk more and write songs and make demos and SO MANY THINGS 😭😭</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-14</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 19:20:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>♡ Timing ♡</title>
            <link>https://www.threads.net/@bailey_lockheart/post/C8VLKPFyMcJ</link>
            <description>at the rate I'm getting this recording done and the amount of time I want to allow myself so I can have presave links/promo videos set up, I might not be releasing anything new until WINTER 😭😭 my fault for not dropping the hanquokka song as a single when I was done with it 🥲💔 I'll start doing singles between big projects after this one, but UGH I really hope I can get this done before it's been a full year since my last release 😭</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-13</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:50:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>♡ Production ♡</title>
            <link>https://www.threads.net/@bailey_lockheart/post/C7fFlO4yXjO</link>
            <description>I need to get better at music production :/ like, two guitar tracks + midi bass and enough harmonies to break my headphones is fun and all, and I'd probably keep those even if I learned to do it better, but I need to at LEAST learn how to play guitar with a metronome without messing up 💀💀 I wanna have fun drums/beats/percussion-y things in my music but idk how to do it yet, and it's hard when my stuff is all human timing :/</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-12</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 13:42:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>♡ Time Management ♡</title>
            <link>https://www.threads.net/@bailey_lockheart/post/C5ccbmSx3f1</link>
            <description><![CDATA[ I wanna make more music but my time management is dead rn 😭 istg once school is over I'll hopefully have calmed down with my brain doing everything to avoid said school, so I'm gonna speedrun production as fast as I can (without making it sound rushed ofc) and get it out asap after that 😭😭 <br><br> <img src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/baileylockheart/rss-feeds/main/images/everskies-skzmeme.jpeg" style="width:300px">]]></description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-11</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 20:02:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>♡ RSS Feed ♡</title>
            <link>https://bailey.lockheart.love/</link>
            <description>I MADE AN RSS FEED 🤩🤩🤩 I felt like I didn't really update this thing enough, and I could just FEEL that it was bc I didn't want to go on my computer to update the html file. Bc of that, I made a little rss feed and stuck it on github so I can use it from my phone!</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-10</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 15:19:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>♡ Country Music???? ♡</title>
            <link>https://www.threads.net/@bailey_lockheart/post/C4pLY5gOoSO</link>
            <description>I FORGOT TO MENTION THIS, but I posted a song that I co-wrote and performed on yt a while back, and today my dad said it popped up on his reccomended as a part of a playlist of country music??? like, I have nothing against country music, but I had no idea that I'd written any 😭😭💀</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-9</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 22:11:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>♡ Small Update ♡</title>
            <link>https://bailey.lockheart.love/</link>
            <description>RECORDING IN PROGRESS 🤩🤩 aaaand also I'm considering adding onto this website 👀 it's a fun little site but I want to make it MORE fun, yknow? idk how I'm gonna do it, but I'll certainly give it a try!</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-8</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 19:34:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>♡ Production ♡</title>
            <link>https://www.threads.net/@bailey_lockheart/post/C23qeVyLR6I</link>
            <description>I wanna learn to do more electronic-y music production 😭😭 it seems so fun + the timing might be easier since you can quantize stuff (or whatever it is) as opposed to trying to line it all up with my 53rd messy take of guitar</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-7</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 19:07:00 -0800</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>♡ Procrastination ♡</title>
            <link>https://baileylockheart.tumblr.com/post/739647921344184321/</link>
            <description>I have a song I SHOULD be working on and I have some songs I WANT to be working on but I will be working on NONE OF THEM</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-6</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 21:33:00 -0800</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>♡ Songwriting Update ♡</title>
            <link>https://bailey.lockheart.love/</link>
            <description>songwriting inspo feels really weird sometimes 🥲 planning out a three song EP, writing a few songs over a week, and now having to sort out a NINE SONG ALBUM??? wild. I miiiight have to cut a song for time, hopefully not, but I wanna get things going!</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-5</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 17:25:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>♡ Microblog ♡</title>
            <link>https://bailey.lockheart.love/</link>
            <description>HEYYYYYYY DIY MICROBLOG??? This whole thing is HEAVILY based on Threads, but I wanted to make something to see if I could! turns out, it's not as hard as I thought it'd be 👀 this doesn't even REALLY have to be a microblog, since there's no character limit! I think this is will be a fun little place for updates and announcements!</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-4</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 08:56:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>♡ New Layout: The Sequel ♡</title>
            <link>https://bailey.lockheart.love/</link>
            <description>uhhhh oops, I redid the whole site bc it was so bad on mobile that it hurt my brain 🥲 aaaanyway, I think this layout's much better than the previous one, so we'll see how it goes!</description>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-3</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 13:12:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>♡ New Layout ♡</title>
            <description>NEW LAYOUTTTTTT 🤩🤩 I coded all of it myself and I'm very proud of it 🥹💖 it might be a little messy right now, but I'm working on it!</description>
            <link>https://bailey.lockheart.love/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-2</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 15:34:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>♡ A Different Place Release! ♡</title>
            <description>I APPARENTLY MADE A MISTAKE, I THOUGHT IT WAS GONNA BE IN MY LOCAL TIMEZONE BUT I THINK IT WAS IN EST, AAAAAA-</description>
            <link>https://bailey.lockheart.love/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">post-1</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 22:51:00 -0700</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
