<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<item>
<pubDate>Mar. 11, 2024</pubDate>
<description>don't ask me why I waited until now to update, idk but RECORDING IN PROGRESS 🤩🤩 aaaand also I'm considering adding onto this website 👀 it's a fun little site but I want to make it MORE fun, yknow? idk how I'm gonna do it, but I'll certainly give it a try!</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubDate>Jan. 15, 2024</pubDate>
<description>I have a song I SHOULD be working on and I have some songs I WANT to be working on but I will be working on NONE OF THEM</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubDate>Nov. 11, 2023</pubDate>
<description>my executive dysfunction doesn’t like me today 😭😭 or maybe it likes me too much</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubDate>Oct. 18, 2023</pubDate>
<description>songwriting inspo feels really weird sometimes 🥲 planning out a three song EP, writing a few songs over a week, and now having to sort out a NINE SONG ALBUM??? wild</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubDate>Sept. 22, 2023</pubDate>
<description>HEYYYYYYY DIY MICROBLOG??? This whole thing is HEAVILY based on Threads, but I wanted to make something to see if I could! turns out, it's not as hard as I thought it'd be 👀 this doesn't even REALLY have to be a microblog, since there's no character limit! I think this is will be a fun little place for updates and announcements!</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubDate>Sept. 17, 2023</pubDate>
<description>uhhhh oops, I redid the whole site bc it was so bad on mobile that it hurt my brain 🥲 aaaanyway, I think this layout's much better than the previous one, so we'll see how it goes!</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubDate>Aug. 26, 2023</pubDate>
<description>NEW LAYOUTTTTTT 🤩🤩 I coded all of it myself and I'm very proud of it 🥹💖 it might be a little messy right now, but I'm working on it!</description>
</item>
<item>
<pubDate>Aug. 20, 2023</pubDate>
<description>I APPARENTLY MADE A MISTAKE, I THOUGHT IT WAS GONNA BE IN MY LOCAL TIMEZONE BUT I THINK IT WAS IN EST, AAAAAA-</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
