<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Lockheart Love: Feeds</title>
<link>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</link>
<item>
<title>fanlistings??</title>
<link>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</link>
<guid>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</guid>
<pubDate>Feb. 11, 2025 15:15:00 PDT</pubDate>
<description>I haven't used this in a bit, but I definitely should ㅠㅠ anyways, I'm working on a section for my fanlistings!! I guess it'll sort of be a fanlistings collective, since I also want to have a section for fanlistings I own/help run... I'm working on it, so we'll have to see how that goes :D</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>blog reconfiguration :/</title>
<link>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</link>
<guid>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</guid>
<pubDate>Dec. 22, 2024 13:46:00 PDT</pubDate>
<description>I initially set up my blog (in the blog section) with the intention of making a suuuuuper easy-to-use blog that I wouldn't have to put effort into formatting, and to be fair, it worked!! But it also got mildly annoying that I can't put pictures or links, and that's discouraged me from using it &#128128; I think I'm gonna redo it so that it's all in html, it shouldn't take that long, but it'll be SO worth it in the end :D</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>domain soon-ish maybe??</title>
<link>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</link>
<guid>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</guid>
<pubDate>Dec. 3, 2024 14:46:00 PDT</pubDate>
<description>I find it a little silly that I have this little microblog-ish thing when I'm on two microblogging platforms and I've very much been regular blogging on this site... but speaking of, I'm currently working on some things that mean that, in essence, I should be able to switch to a neocities domain relatively soon! That's not a HUGE promise considering that I mean relatively in the sense that it took me eight months to get this site up in the first place, but it is a promise nonetheless :'D </description>
</item>
<item>
<title>FINALLYYYYYYYYYY</title>
<link>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</link>
<guid>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</guid>
<pubDate>Nov. 30, 2024 20:46:00 PDT</pubDate>
<description>yet another disappearance and a surprising(?) amount of work later, but FINALLY THE SITE IS HOSTED!!! Currently, it's up on Netlify, and that's already working pretty well! Still, I do intend to put this thing on Neocities, it's just a matter of when :') while one wait is finally over, another begins, and I'M LIVING FOR IT TBH BC I'M VERY EXCITED</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>oops</title>
<link>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</link>
<guid>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</guid>
<pubDate>July 20, 2024 11:55:00 PDT</pubDate>
<description>I disappeared for a long time, but I'm back to working on this site hehe ^^ I've got like one more section I want to work on before I can put it up? but yeah!! website!! :D</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Final PROJECT??</title>
<link>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</link>
<guid>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</guid>
<pubDate>May 13, 2024 15:32:00 PDT</pubDate>
<description>I used a draft version of this website for a final project 🤩🤩 I thought I was being sneaky abt it lol, but regardless, school is wrapping up soon so HOPEFULLY I'll be able to get all my website stuff set up soon ^^</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Final Section</title>
<link>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</link>
<guid>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</guid>
<pubDate>Mar. 28, 2024 12:52:00 PDT</pubDate>
<description>I'm getting through this WAYYY faster than I expected, even though I still can't host it for a few months 😔 although, I do have one section left that idk what to do with. I don't want to dedicate myself to a text blog when I know I won't end up doing it, and I don't want to make a music section when I have an entire website dedicated to my music, so what so I do?? I'll have to figure it out at some point, but still 😭</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Web Design Class</title>
<link>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</link>
<guid>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</guid>
<pubDate>Mar. 25, 2024 17:41:00 PDT</pubDate>
<description>I'm setting this up still and ik I won't be making it public for a long time but IT'S SO FUN 😭😭 Also I'm specifically making a shrine abt Madds Buckley bc,,, obviously I am, though I literally just ripped off my own design that I made for my web design class 😭 tbf I literally did that assignment about her, so at least it's not like I didn't make it about her in the first place 🫠</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Testing Testing 123</title>
<link>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</link>
<guid>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</guid>
<pubDate>Mar. 24, 2024 8:11:00 PDT</pubDate>
<description><![CDATA[ I just wanna test out something, soooo- HEY LOOK, A BUTTON! <br><br> <img src="http://baileylockheart.netlify.app/images/button.gif"><br><br> okay,,,, hopefully that works 😭 I'm very much new to this whole rss feed thing, but I wanna be able to use html type stuff in it, too! I like the idea of turning this into a full-on microblog thing as opposed to the one on my music site, which is more simple. I should probably add the titles to that one though 🥲 ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
<title>B R A I N R O T</title>
<link>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</link>
<guid>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</guid>
<pubDate>Mar. 23, 2024 23:44:00 PDT</pubDate>
<description>why is the concept of a new website tearing my brain apart from the inside out 😭😭 like I am SO invested, I'm away from my computer bc I'm supposed to be sleeping and even now I just CAN'T. STOP. THINKING?? Like I'm literally using this bc I already said gn on threads (my main social media) and now I'm scrolling on tumblr of all places, looking at people saying fun it is to make a website</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hihi ^^</title>
<link>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</link>
<guid>https://lockheartlove.neocities.org/feeds</guid>
<pubDate>Mar. 23, 2024 10:46:00 PDT</pubDate>
<description>NEW WEBSITE NEW WEBSITE!!! I'm very excited abt this one since it's my first fully personal, not-in-character-as-someone-else, personal site! I'm still working out what to put in it, and as of writing this, the website it's meant for actually isn't up yet, but I'm gonna keep updating this as I go :D</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
